Hi, in this lesson, you will learn about the Edge inside panel in Google Antigravica.
This is a powerful AI assistance that lives in your sidebar and helps you understand
the code, make changes across multiple files and work more efficiently.
So, let me start what is the Edge inside panel.
It is the AI coordinate system, so I think you can think of it as having experience
a developer sitting next to you and ready to answer your questions and help with any coding
tasks.
So, unlike pub and command features, which work in line, the Edge inside panel gives you
a dedicated space to have longer conversations with AI about your code.
You can also extend this window and have a bigger place where you can see and chat with
AI.
So, let's start with understanding the interface, yeah?
So, at the top of the panel, you will see the plus icon, so you can start in new conversations
whenever you like a fresh start.
This is helpful when you want to switch between different tasks or topics.
Like, the first question was about generating the feature and another question was about
generating the feature.
For example, another feature.
So, then it's better to start in a new chart, yeah?
Edge conversation keeps its own history and context, so you can organize your work by
feature, by bug fixes, or any other way that makes sense of your workflow, yeah?
So, you have a text input where you can type anything you want.
You can also attach some files.
For example, images, so if you click plus, you can attach images, or you can just drag
and drop it here, so it will read the images.
If you, for example, like to build some component, which look like a few screenshot, then
you can attach it and it will build the same, yeah?
You can also do the mentions and workflows, we'll talk about it in separate lessons because
I will have a lot to talk you about these features, so we'll come back to them later, yeah?
But also, since it's called context and context help, yeah, better understand what you're
working on and what you'd like, so it's more context you will give to AI, it's the more
expected and precise response you will get, so the next one is agent mode.
It's also important feature, because it's ability to switch between the different type
of work, yeah?
We'll cover these modes in the tail, in next lessons, but can I just know we have the
planning mode and you have past mode, so I'll show you some examples how to work with
it a bit later, yeah?
And just to say in short, some of mode is good for planning and it's when you'd like
to work on more complex features and the past mode just for some quick answers.
So you can also choose the different AI models, yeah?
Some of models are faster and great for simple tasks and they take less credits and
some of models better for difficult tasks, for investigation, for thinking, et cetera, and
they're more powerful, yet I already explained it about this models in one of the previous
lessons about overview of AI models, so you can back with the lessons to better understand
what this model is best for and choose the model will work for you.
Okay, in general, you can track your progress in this conversation, anti-gravity help
you stay organized, yeah?
Also, when you're working in a chat, let me click this switch to the history, so if I click
here, you can see the past conversations, and right here, you can see also the changes you
have from our small changes, yeah, because you just ask, yeah, but in next lessons, I will
show you how to use it in more details, because you'll do the refactoring of the code,
you'll write in new code using the agent, and you'll have many changes and it can explain
you how you can review the code and et cetera.
So, let's wrap up, maybe understand what is the agent's site panel, what you can do
with this interface, you know where to find this editor, how to create new conversation,
how to attach some files, context and et cetera.
So, in the next lesson, we will dive deeper into agent modes, into complex options, what
is it, how to use it, and how to get most out of this power full with EIS system.
Okay, see you in the next lesson.